Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Legal Work and Client Files, 1915-1992
  - UFWA, Local 140: The Englander Company, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Flex-O-Air Sleep Products, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Globe Mattress Company, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Gould Plastic Products, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Greenwich Mattress Company, 1957-1959 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Harlem Mattress Company, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Harris Linen Company, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Hauptman Feather Company, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Hein & Koping, Inc., 1963 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Henry Products, Inc., 1968 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Howard Rubber Company, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Hudson Mattress Company, 1957-1958 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Imperial Sleep Products, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Imperial Sleep Products and Sleepmaker Bedding Corporation, 1952, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Independent Mattress Company, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Wm. Intner Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Jerome Furniture Company, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Joseph A. Kaplan & Sons, Inc., 1957-1959, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Kaynard, Samuel M. v. Local 140, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products Company (Ernest Kohn and Menashe Birnbaum) v. Local 140- Appellate Division Brief, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Formal, 1964-Feb 1965 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Formal, Mar 1965 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Formal, Apr 1965-Nov 1965 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Formal, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Memoranda, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Notes and Related Materials, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - UFWA, Local 140: K&B Foam Products v. Local 140- Original Papers, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - UFWA, Local 140: M&G Sheet Metal, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Manhattan Felting Mills, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Maybrook Bedding - Delwar Corporation, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 39)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Metallized Carbon v. Local 140- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 40)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Metallized Carbon v. Local 140- NLRB, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 41)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Metallized Carbon v. Local 140- Westchester County Supreme Court, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Minter, Bernard, 1951, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - UFWA, Local 140: M.Mittman & Company, Inc. v. Alex Sirota, 1951, Undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Mittman v. Sirota- Formal File, Defendants-Appellants' Proposed Case on Appeal, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Mittman v. Sirota- Formal File, Examination of the Plaintiff (I), 1951 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Mittman v. Sirota- Formal File, Examination of the Plaintiff (II), 1951 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Mittman v. Sirota- Formal File, Trial Transcript (I), 1951 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Mittman v. Sirota- Formal File, Trial Transcript (II), 1951 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Modern Pillow Company, 1961-1963 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Modern Stores, Inc., 1965 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Molded Plastic Button Corporation, 1965-1968 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Moon Bedding Company, Inc. and George Richardson, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Morales, Benjamin, 1960, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - UFWA, Local 140: National Bedding and Upholstery Manufacturers, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - UFWA, Local 140: National Bedspring Company, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Nau, Josephine and Paul, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Negotiations, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - UFWA, Local 140: New York Bedding Manufacturers Association, 1950-1962 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - UFWA, Local 140: North Brooklyn Supply Company - Contract and Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - UFWA, Local 140: North Brooklyn Supply Company - Formal, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - UFWA, Local 140: North Brooklyn Supply Company - Original Papers and Various Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Original Venetian Blind Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Paramount Feather Company, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Paunetto, Carlos, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Pension Fund - Winick, Emil, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - UFWA, Local 140: People of the State of New York v. Alex Sirot a (I), 1954-1955 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - UFWA, Local 140: People of the State of New York v. Alex Sirota(II), 1954-1955 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - UFWA, Local 140: People of the State of New York v. Alex Sirota(III), 1954-1955 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Perez, Pedro v. Lorraine Fiber Mills, Inc., 1954 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Purofied Down Products Corporation - Arbitration (Chaney, Eddie), 1964 (Box 103, Folder 30)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Purofied Down Products Corporation - Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 103, Folder 31)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Purofied Down Products Corporation - Formal, Various Cases, Hearings and Arbitrations, 1959-1965 (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Purofied Down Products Corporation - Various Notes, Press, Exhibits and Related Documents, 1960-1965 (Box 103, Folder 33)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Quiroz, Carlos v. Local 140, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Rehabilitation Council, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Restyme Products, Inc., 1955 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Rightway Mattress Company, Inc. (I), 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Rightway Mattress Company, Inc. (II), 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Ritz Cotton Felt Company, Inc. and New England Folding Cot Corporation, 1957, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sanford Drapery, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sani-Aqua, Inc., 1965 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Schwartz Mattress Company, 1951-1955 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sealy Greater New York, Inc. and The Waterbury Mattress Company, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Auditors' Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Consultants' Proposal (Pension), Undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Hirsch & Co. Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Minutes (Pension), 1952-1959 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Minutes (Security), 1951-1966 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security and Pension Funds - Portfolio Analysis and Recommendations, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Allen, Robert, 1963 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Automatic Bedding Corporation Loan, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Brooklyn Jewish Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Fine, Mildred, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Forms, 1960, Undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Jackson, Blondell, 1963 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Kozlowicz, Helen, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - McRae, Robert, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Monti, Joseph, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Moore, Ethel, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Pagette, Louise, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Parris, Katie, 1963 (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Pendarvis, Rebecca, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Petrillo, Michael, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Pierson, William, 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Pirro, Virginia, 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Rodriguez, Juan, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Security Fund - Silberman and Casper, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sleep Products, Inc. - Bankrupt, 1954-1955 (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sleepnite Bedding Corporation, 1960, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 37)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Slomowitz, David and Slomowitz, Arnold v. Local 140, et al., 1957 (Box 104, Folder 38)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Standard Mattress Company, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Supreme Felt Company, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 40)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Sussman Manufacturing Company, 1969-1970 (Box 104, Folder 41)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Terry, James, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 42)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Tischler v. Pearl's Surprise Laundry, 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 43)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company, 1964-1967 (Box 104, Folder 44)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Briefs and Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 45)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 104, Folder 46)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Formal, 1965-1968 (Box 104, Folder 47)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Original Papers, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 48)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Proceedings, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Mattress Company - Research, Undated (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation, 1960, 1962, Undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation - Arbitration, 1964-1966 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation - Formal, 1962-1963 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation - Local 819 v. U.S. Pillow and Local 140, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - UFWA, Local 140: U.S. Pillow Corporation v. McLeod, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Voice of 140, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1953 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Wilk and Smerling Brothers, 1964-1967 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Case #68, 1956 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Correspondence, 1951-Jul 1953 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Correspondence, Aug 1953-1955 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Eldridge, Hope Tisdale, 1949-1953 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Glassman, Sidney, 1946-1953 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Harris, Jack Sargent, 1947-1953 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Various Individuals, 1951-1955 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - United Nations Administrative Tribunal: Various Notes, Drafts, Fragments, Articles, Memoranda, 1952-1956, Undated (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA): Durkin, James v. Emil Rieve, [1949]-[1959] (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - UOPWA: Paris, Phillip, et al. v. Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, et al.- Correspondence, 1945-1952, Undated (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Formal, 1948, Oct 1950 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Formal, Nov 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Formal, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Formal, Apr 1951 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Formal, May 1951-Jun 1951, Undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Various Notes, Drafts, Fragments, Memoranda, Newsletters and Lists (I), 1944-1951, Undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - UOPWA: Paris v. Metropolitan Life - Various Notes, Drafts, Fragments, Memoranda, Newsletters and Lists (II), 1944-1951, Undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - UOPWA, Local 30: Durkin, James v. Simon Helfgott, et al., 1950 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - UOPWA, Local 96: Arbitration between Financial Employees Guild and Title Guarantee and Trust Company, 1948 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - UOPWA, Local 231 (Metropolitan Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians): Douds, Charles (NLRB) v. Local 231, [1947] (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - UOPWA, Local 1706 (Industrial Insurance Employees Union): Durkin, James v. John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, [1950] (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Kuykendall, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Mitchell(Watergate): Partial Transcript of Jury Charge, Undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Samuel Loring Morison, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - War Resisters League, 1915-1958 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - War Resisters League, 1962-1974 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - War Resisters League: Similar Statements of American Friends Service Committee (AFSC), 1941-1974 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - War Resisters League: Tax Resistance, 1935-1971, Undated (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - War Resisters League: Tax Resistance, 1972-1974 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Washington Mobilization Committee, et al. v. Cullinane, Maurice, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Watergate-Related Exhibits, 1969-1971 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Wein, Charles: re:Jose Miguel Esposito Carbonell, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Weinfurtner, Richard P.: Alleged Libel, 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Weinman, Nettie: Possible FBI Harassment, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Weinstein, Benjamin C., 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Weinstock, Edward: Draft Question, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Weisman, Maxwell: Passport, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Weiss, Morris: Security Clearance, 1960-1961 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Weissberg, Ken: Communist Party Membership, Substitute Teaching License, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 26)
  - Whyte, Eloise: Alien Employment, 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - Wickham v. Trapani(Apple Growers' Appeal), 1966 (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - Wilder, Emzie: re: Shooting Death of John Wesley Wilder by Ruston, LA Police, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - Worthy, William v. John Foster Dulles(Passport): Yale Moot Court, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - Wounded Knee: Various Cases, 1973-1975 (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - Wounded Knee: Various Cases, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Wounded Knee: Various Cases, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Zlatovski, Jane Foster: Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - Zlatovski, Jane Foster: Estates / Formal, 1969-1973 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - Zlatovski, Jane Foster: USA v. George Zlatovski, [1957] (Box 106, Folder 36)